所以你该如何将UI打碎成更小的组件呢？
So how did you break up the UI
into smaller components?
好，你可能会认为这会是两列。
Well, you might've thought that
this could be two columns.
但是这样有一个元素却很难定位，这里。
But then it would be hard to
position the elements here.
你可以把它们垂直居中于屏幕的高度里。
You could center them vertically
within the height of the screen.
但是它不一定会和左侧的温度视图
But it wouldn't necessarily line up
with the temperature views on the left
对齐。
hand side.
实际上这看起来更像一个水平布局。
Instead this looks more like
a horizontal linear layout.
然后其它视图就可以使用一个垂直的线性布局
Then the rest of the elements could
be laid out by using a vertical
来排列。
linear layout.
这个垂直线性布局会有六个子元素。
The vertical linear layout
would have six children.
第三个元素会是一个水平线性布局，它由两个子元素组成
The third element would be a horizontal
linear layout composed of two children.
第一个会是另一个垂直线性布局，它有两个文本视图，
The first would be another vertical
linear layout with these two text views
第二个视图会是另一个垂直线性布局，
and the second element would be another
vertical linear layout composed of.
包含这两个元素。
These two elements.
要使全屏的内容可以滚动，
To make the contents of the whole
screen vertically scrollable
我们把它放到一个scrollview里。
we put it inside a scroll view.
在这里使用listView会有点多余，因为我们不需要扩展
Using a list view here would be overkill
because we don't need to scale
到无限数量的项，我们也不需要回收。
to an infinite number of item and
we don't need recycling.
这里屏幕上的域是固定的
There's a fixed number of
fields on the screen so
所以scrollView是最完美的选择。
the scroll view is the perfect choice.
我可以向你展示我们为fragment_detail.xml布局的实现。
I can show you our implementation for
the fragment detail XML layout.
我们硬编码了一些数据在layout中，
We hardcoded some data in the layout.
这样它就会在设计面板中作为预览来展示。
So that it would show up as
a preview in the Design pane.
在视图层级的根节点，我们有一个ScrollView。
At the root of the view hierarchy,
we have a ScrollView.
ScrollView只能有最多一个子元素。
ScrollViews can only have max one child.
所以我们将其设为垂直线性布局。
So we set that to be
the vertical LinearLayout.
在这个布局中，我们有一个文本视图给周几。
Inside of this layout, we have
a TextView for the day of the week.
日历日期，以及一个水平线性布局。
The calendar date and
then a horizontal linear layout.
紧接着是一个湿度文本视图，
This is followed by
the humidity text view,
风力文本视图，以及气压文本视图。
wind text view, and pressure text view.
在XML代码中，我们看到ScrollView，包含有一水平布局子视图。
In the XML code we see the scroll
view with the child linear layout.
我们给它一点16dp的内间距，
We give it some padding of 16 dips so
所以内容不会贴在屏幕边上。
that the content is not flesh up
against the edge of the screen.
然后我们看到文本视图，紧挨着是水平线性布局。
Then we see the text views followed
by the horizontal linear layout.
我们指定布局margin top为16dp，
We specify layout margin top of 16 dip
来让它离开这个文本视图的底部一些距离。
to give it some more space from
the bottom of this text view.
在这个水平线性布局中，我们有一个垂直线性布局。
Within this horizontal linear layout
we have one vertical linear layout.
它的宽度为0，权重为1，
Which has a width of 0 and
a weight of 1, and
且另一个线性布局的宽度是0权重也是1。
another linear layout with
a width of 0 and a weight of 1.
也就是说每一个子元素都有相同的宽度。
That means that both of these
children have equal width.
对于这些线性布局，我们定义gravity为center_horizontal。
For this linear layout, we specify
gravity to be center horizontal.
这意味着其中的内容将会是垂直居中的。
That means that the contents inside
of it will be centered horizontally.
这包含了icon和forecast文本视图。
Which includes the icon as well
as the forecast text view.
最后我们还有些剩余的针对其它天气细节的文本视图。
Lastly we have the remaining text
views for the other weather details.
当布局看起来不错了，我们更新DetailFragemnt。
When the layout looks good,
we update the detail fragment.
现在，我们同时把它放到它自己的文件里去。
At this point,
we also move it into its own file.
在onLoadFinish方法中，
In the onload finish method,
我们习惯于有一个findViewById调用，来找到文本视图。
we used to have a find view by
ID call to find the text view.
现在DetailFragment有了更多的视图。
Now that the detail fragment
has a lot more views
我们不希望继续在这里加更多的findViewById调用。
we don't want to continue adding even
more find view by ID calls here.
因为它必须要在每次加载器更新的时候
Because it will have to traverse
the view hierarchy every time that
遍历视图层级。
the loader refreshes.
与之相反，我们修改onCreate方法。
Instead we modify the on create method.
一旦Fragment初始化了，我们就继续
Once the fragment is
inflated we go ahead and
找到对所有视图的引用，稍后用到。
find a reference to all the views
we are going to need later on.
我们把这些视图存作这个类的成员变量。
We store these views as member
variables of the class,
所以它们的命名都以字母m开头。
which is why the name
starts with the letter m.
在onCreateLoader方法中，我们确保从内容提供器
In the on create loader method we
make sure that the projection for
中查询的映射包含了所有我们需要的信息。
our content provider query contains
all the information that we need.
它在文件的顶部定义了。
It's declared at the top of the file.
之前我们叫它FORECAST_COLUMNS，但
Before we had it called
forecast columns, but
现在我们称之为DETAIL_COLUMNS。
we just renamed it to detail columns.
我们也多加了一些列，因为现在我们要在屏幕上
And we also added some more columns
because now we're displaying more
展示更多信息。
information on the screen.
然后，在onLoadFinished方法中我们得到一个游标指向了我们需要的所有数据。
Then in the onLoadFinished method we get
a cursor back with the data we need.
我们从游标中读取weather_condition_id，
We read the weather
condition ID from the cursor
因为我们需要用它来检查该用哪幅图片，
because we're going to need it to
determine which image to display but for
不过现在我们可以使用一副占位图标。
now we can use a place holder icon.
我们继续从游标里读取日期，描述
We continue reading from the cursor
to get the date, the description and
和其它域。
the other fields.
要为用户妥善格式化数据，我们还需要从代码片段中
To format the data properly for the user
we also copied over the strings and
拷贝字符串和工具方法。
the utility method from the gist.